<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Auto Backup | Stash on GitHub for Kubernetes</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/</link><description>Recent content in Auto Backup | Stash on GitHub for Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Auto Backup Databases | Stash</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/database/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/database/</guid><description>Auto Backup for Database This tutorial will show you how to configure automatic backup for PostgreSQL database using Stash. Here, we are going to backup two different PostgreSQL databases of two different version using a common blueprint.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube.</description></item><item><title>Auto Backup Overview | Stash</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/overview/</guid><description>Auto Backup with Stash Stash can be configured to automatically backup of any stateful workloads in your cluster. Stash enables cluster administrators to deploy backup blueprints ahead of time so that application owners can easily backup any types of workload with a few annotations. This allows Enterprises to stay prepared for disaster scenarios and recover from offsite secure backups in case of a disaster on public cloud and on-premises datacenters.</description></item><item><title>Auto Backup PVC | Stash</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/pvc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/pvc/</guid><description>Auto Backup for PVC This tutorial will show you how to configure automatic backup for PersistentVolumeClaims. Here, we are going to backup a PVC provisioned from an NFS server using auto-backup.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube.</description></item><item><title>Auto Backup Workload | Stash</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/workload/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/auto-backup/workload/</guid><description>Auto Backup for Workloads This tutorial will show you how to configure automatic backup for Kubernetes workloads. Here, we are going to show a demo on how we can backup Deployments, StatefulSets, and DaemonSets using a common blueprint.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one using Minikube.</description></item></channel></rss>