<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Types of Alerts on The Kubernetes Company</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/5.1.1/concepts/alert-types/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Types of Alerts on The Kubernetes Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/5.1.1/concepts/alert-types/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cluster Alert Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/5.1.1/concepts/alert-types/cluster-alert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/5.1.1/concepts/alert-types/cluster-alert/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
ClusterAlerts  What is ClusterAlert A ClusterAlert is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definition (CRD). It provides declarative configuration of Icinga services for cluster level alerts in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired check command and notifier in a ClusterAlert object, and the Searchlight operator will create Icinga2 hosts, services and notifications to the desired state for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node Alert Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/5.1.1/concepts/alert-types/node-alert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/5.1.1/concepts/alert-types/node-alert/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 NodeAlerts What is NodeAlert A NodeAlert is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definition (CRD). It provides declarative configuration of Icinga services for Nodes in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired check command and notifier in a NodeAlert object, and the Searchlight operator will create Icinga2 hosts, services and notifications to the desired state for you.
NodeAlert Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, a NodeAlert needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pod Alert Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/5.1.1/concepts/alert-types/pod-alert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/5.1.1/concepts/alert-types/pod-alert/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 PodAlerts What is PodAlert A PodAlert is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definition (CRD). It provides declarative configuration of Icinga services for Pods in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired check command and notifier in a PodAlert object, and the Searchlight operator will create Icinga2 hosts, services and notifications to the desired state for you.
PodAlert Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, a PodAlert needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>