<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Setup | Stash on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Setup | Stash on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Install</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/install/</guid>
      <description>Installation Guide Using YAML Stash can be installed using YAML files includes in the /hack/deploy folder.
# Install without RBAC roles $ kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/appscode/stash/0.6.0/hack/deploy/without-rbac.yaml # Install with RBAC roles $ kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/appscode/stash/0.6.0/hack/deploy/with-rbac.yaml  Using Helm Stash can be installed via Helm using the chart included in this repository or from official charts repository. To install the chart with the release name my-release:
$ helm repo update $ helm install stable/stash --name my-release  To see the detailed configuration options, visit here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Table of Contents | Setup</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/</guid>
      <description> Setup Setup contains instructions for installing the Stash and its various components in Kubernetes.
 Install Stash. Installation instructions for Stash. Uninstall Stash. Instructions for uninstallating Stash. Upgrading Stash. Instructions for upgrading Stash. Developer Guide  Overview. Outlines everything you need to know from setting up your dev environment to how to build and test Stash. Release process. Steps for releasing a new version of Stash.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/uninstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/uninstall/</guid>
      <description>Uninstall Stash Please follow the steps below to uninstall Stash:
 Delete the deployment and service used for Stash operator. ```console $ ./hack/deploy/uninstall.sh kubectl delete deployment -l app=stash -n kube-system deployment &amp;ldquo;stash-operator&amp;rdquo; deleted kubectl delete service -l app=stash -n kube-system service &amp;ldquo;stash-operator&amp;rdquo; deleted kubectl delete secret -l app=stash -n kube-system No resources found kubectl delete serviceaccount -l app=stash -n kube-system No resources found kubectl delete clusterrolebindings -l app=stash -n kube-system No resources found kubectl delete clusterrole -l app=stash -n kube-system No resources found kubectl delete initializerconfiguration -l app=stash initializerconfiguration &amp;ldquo;stash-initializer&amp;rdquo; deleted ```</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.0/setup/upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Upgrading Stash Upgrading from 0.5.1 to 0.6.0 The format for Restic object has changed in backward incompatiable manner between 0.5.x and 0.6.0 . The steps involved in upgrading Stash operator to 0.6.0 from prior version involves the following steps:
 Backup all your old Restic CRDs. Delete your old Restic objects. It will stop taking backups and remove sidecars from pods. Uninstall old Stash operator. Move repositories to new location if you want to keep your old backups.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>