<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs | Stash on The Kubernetes Company</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs | Stash on The Kubernetes Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Acknowledgement | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/acknowledgement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/acknowledgement/</guid>
      <description> Acknowledgement  Many thanks to Alexander Neumann for Restic project.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/contributing/</guid>
      <description>Contribution Guidelines Want to hack on Stash?
AppsCode projects are Apache 2.0 licensed and accept contributions via GitHub pull requests. This document outlines some of the conventions on development workflow, commit message formatting, contact points and other resources to make it easier to get your contribution accepted.
Certificate of Origin By contributing to this project you agree to the Developer Certificate of Origin (DCO). This document was created by the Linux Kernel community and is a simple statement that you, as a contributor, have the legal right to make the contribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Project Status Versioning Policy There are 2 parts to versioning policy:
 Operator version: Stash does not follow semver. Currently Stash operator implementation is considered alpha. Please report any issues you via Github. Once released, the major version of operator is going to point to the Kubernetes client-go version. You can verify this from the glide.yaml file. This means there might be breaking changes between point releases of the operator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/support/</guid>
      <description>Support We use Slack for public discussions. To chit chat with us or the rest of the community, join us in the AppsCode Slack team channel #stash. To sign up, use our Slack inviter.
If you have found a bug with Stash or want to request for new features, please file an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weclome | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.1/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Stash Stash by AppsCode is a Kubernetes operator for restic. If you are running production workloads in Kubernetes, you might want to take backup of your disks. Using Stash, you can backup Kubernetes volumes mounted in following types of workloads:
 Deployment DaemonSet ReplicaSet ReplicationController StatefulSet  From here you can learn all about Stash&amp;rsquo;s architecture and how to deploy and use Stash.
 Concepts. Concepts explain some significant aspect of Stash.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>