<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Legal | AppsCode on GitHub for Kubernetes</title><link>https://appscode.com/legal/</link><description>Recent content in Legal | AppsCode on GitHub for Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://appscode.com/legal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://appscode.com/legal/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/legal/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Personal Data, Information Access and Deletion Personal Data AppsCode is committed to protect user personal information. Users are advised not to disclose any personal information or data to any third party to avoid unauthorized access, use or disclosure until and otherwise the third party is entitled to retain such information. However, AppsCode may not totally eliminate such security risks which are associated with the collection, disclosure and storage of user information, which may lead to mistakes and security breaches.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://appscode.com/legal/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/legal/security/</guid><description>AppsCode addresses security as a very important factor and takes best possible measure to ensure secured services. AppsCode maintains best practises to secure users from vulnerabilities using security controls over data and updates security features on regular basis.
Reporting Security Issues If you notice any vulnerabilities in AppsCode services, immediately report by email to security@appscode.com with the details. AppsCode appreciates working with bug reporter(s) to fix bug promptly. You can report vulnerabilities securely using the following PGP key.</description></item><item><title>Service Level Agreement</title><link>https://appscode.com/legal/sla/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/legal/sla/</guid><description>AppsCode Service Level Agreement(SLA) is a policy applicable upon the usage of AppsCode hosted plans subjected to the AppsCode Terms of Service. In accordance with the Terms of Service, AppsCode reserve the rights to amend the SLA.
1. Commitment of Service With a Monthly Uptime Percentage (defined below) of at least 99.9%, AppsCode will make precedence available individually for any annual/monthly billing cycle. In due course if AppsCode can not meet the Commitment of Service, user will be eligible to receive a Service Credit as mentioned beneath.</description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://appscode.com/legal/tos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/legal/tos/</guid><description>AppsCode welcomes you to the Terms of Service! Please read this document very carefully before using services. This document has been made to protect both you and AppsCode authority. Once you click “Sign up” you are agreeing your acceptance to use AppsCode Services bound by these Terms of Service.
1. Agreement The use of Appscode services is legally bound by this Agreement and AppsCode has the right to update and change the Terms of Service from time to time without notice.</description></item></channel></rss>