<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Declarative API | Stash on The Kubernetes Company</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Declarative API | Stash on The Kubernetes Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AppBinding Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/appbinding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/appbinding/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 AppBinding What is AppBinding Stash needs to know how to connect with a target database and the credentials necessary to access it. This is done via an AppBinding.
An AppBinding is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition(CRD) which points to an application using either its URL (usually for a non-Kubernetes resident service instance) or a Kubernetes service object (if self-hosted in a Kubernetes cluster), some optional parameters and a credential secret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BackupBlueprint Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/backupblueprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/backupblueprint/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 BackupBlueprint What is BackupBlueprint Stash uses 1-1 mapping among Repository, BackupConfiguration and the target. So, whenever you want to backup a target(workload/PV/PVC/database), you have to create a Repository and BackupConfiguration object. This could become tiresome when you are trying to backup similar types of target and the Repository and BackupConfiguration has only slight difference. To mitigate this problem, Stash provides a way to specify a blueprint for these two objects via BackupBlueprint crd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BackupConfiguration Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/backupconfiguration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/backupconfiguration/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 BackupConfiguration What is BackupConfiguration A BackupConfiguration is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition(CRD) which specifies the backup target, parameters(schedule, retention policy etc.) and a Repository object that holds snapshot storage information in a Kubernetes native way.
You have to create a BackupConfiguration object for each backup target. A backup target can be a workload, database or a PV/PVC.
BackupConfiguration CRD Specification Like any official Kubernetes resource, a BackupConfiguration has TypeMeta, ObjectMeta and Spec sections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BackupSession Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/backupsession/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/backupsession/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 BackupSession What is BackupSession A BackupSession is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition(CRD) which represents a backup run of the respective target referenced by a BackupConfiguration in a Kubernetes native way.
Stash operator creates a Kubernetes CronJob according to the schedule defined in a BackupConfiguration. On each backup schedule, this CronJob creates a BackupSession object. It points to the respective BackupConfiguration. The controller that runs inside backup sidecar (in case of backup via jobs, it is stash operator itself) watches this BackupSession object and start taking backup instantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Function Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/function/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/function/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Function What is Function A complete backup or restore process may consist of several steps. For example, in order to backup a PostgreSQL database we first need to dump the database and upload the dumped file to a backend. Then we need to update the respectiveRepository and BackupSession status and send Prometheus metrics. In Stash, we call such individual steps a Function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repository Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/repository/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/repository/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Repository What is Repository A Repository is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition(CRD) which represents backend information in a Kubernetes native way.
You have to create a Repository object for each backup target. Since v1beta1 api, a Repository object has 1-1 mapping with a target. Thus, only one target can be backed up into one Repository.
Repository CRD Specification Like any official Kubernetes resource, a Repostiory object has TypeMeta, ObjectMeta, Spec and Status sections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RestoreSession Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/restoresession/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/restoresession/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 RestoreSession What is RestoreSession A RestoreSession is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition(CRD) which specifies a target to restore and the source of data that will be restored in a Kubernetes native way.
You have to create a RestoreSession object whenever you want to restore. When a RestoreSession object is created, Stash injects an init-container into the target workload and restarts it. The init-container restores the desired data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapshot Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/snapshot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/snapshot/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Snapshot What is Snapshot A Snapshot is a representation of backup snapshot in a Kubernetes native way. Stash uses an Aggregated API Server to provide get and list capabilities for snapshots from the backend.
This enables you to view some useful information such as creationTimestamp, snapshot id, backed up path etc of a snapshot. This also provides the capability to restore a specific snapshot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/task/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/task/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Task What is Task An entire backup or restore process needs an ordered execution of one or more steps. A Function represents a step of a backup or restore process. A Task is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition(CRD) which specifies a sequence of functions along with their parameters in a Kubernetes native way.
When you install Stash, some Tasks will be pre-installed for supported targets like databases, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>