<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Volume Snapshot | Stash on The Kubernetes Company</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Volume Snapshot | Stash on The Kubernetes Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapshot Deployment Volumes | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/deployment/</guid>
      <description>Snapshotting the volumes of a Deployment This guide will show you how to use Stash to snapshot the volumes of a Deployment and restore them from snapshot using Kubernetes VolumeSnapshot API. In this guide, we are going to backup the volumes in Google Cloud Platform with the help of GCE Persistent Disk CSI Driver.
Before You Begin  At first, you need to be familiar with the GCE Persistent Disk CSI Driver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapshot Stand-alone PVC | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/pvc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/pvc/</guid>
      <description>Snapshotting a Standalone PVC This guide will show you how to use Stash to snapshot standalone PersistentVolumeClaims and restore that from snapshot using Kubernetes VolumeSnapshot API. In this guide, we are going to backup the volumes in Google Cloud Platform with the help of GCE Persistent Disk CSI Driver.
Before You Begin  At first, you need to be familiar with the GCE Persistent Disk CSI Driver. You need to enable the Kubernetes VolumeSnapshotDataSource alpha feature via Kubernetes feature gates  --feature-gates=VolumeSnapshotDataSource=true  Install Stash in your cluster following the steps here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapshot StatefulSet Volumes | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/statefulset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/statefulset/</guid>
      <description>Snapshotting the volumes of a StatefulSet This guide will show you how to use Stash to snapshot the volumes of a StatefulSets and restore them from snapshot using Kubernetes VolumeSnapshot API. In this guide, we are going to backup the volumes in Google Cloud Platform with the help of GCE Persistent Disk CSI Driver.
Before You Begin  At first, you need to be familiar with the GCE Persistent Disk CSI Driver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VolumeSnapshot Overview | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/volumesnapshot/overview/</guid>
      <description>How VolumeSnapshot works in Stash This guide will show you how Stash takes snapshot of PersistentVolumeClaims and restore them from snapshot using Kubernetes VolumeSnapshot API.
Before You Begin  At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster and ensure that a CSI driver that implements snapshots is deployed on your cluster. You can find a list of CSI drivers that supports snapshots here. In this guide we are going to use GCE Persistent Disk CSI Driver.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>