<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Backends | Stash on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Backends | Stash on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS S3/Minio/Rook Backend | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/s3/</guid>
      <description>AWS S3 Stash supports AWS S3 or S3 compatible storage services like Minio servers, Rook Object Store, DigitalOceans Space as a backend. This tutorial will show you how to use this backend.
In order to use S3 or S3 compatible storage service as backend, you have to create a Secret and a Repository object pointing to the desired bucket.
Create Storage Secret To configure storage secret for this backend, following secret keys are needed:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Backend | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/azure/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Azure Storage Stash supports Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure Blob Storage as a backend. This tutorial will show you how to use this backend.
In order to use Azure Blob Storage as backend, you have to create a Secret and a Repository object pointing to the desired blob container.
Create Storage Secret To configure storage secret for this backend, following secret keys are needed:
   Key Type Description     RESTIC_PASSWORD Required Password that will be used to encrypt the backup snapshots   AZURE_ACCOUNT_NAME Required Azure Storage account name   AZURE_ACCOUNT_KEY Required Azure Storage account key    Create storage secret as below,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backblaze B2 Backend | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/b2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/b2/</guid>
      <description>Backblaze B2 Stash supports Backblaze&amp;rsquo;s B2 Cloud Storage as a backend. This tutorial will show you how to use this backend.
In order to use Backblaze B2 Cloud Storage as backend, you have to create a Secret and a Repository object pointing to the desired B2 bucket.
Create Storage Secret To configure storage secret for this backend, following secret keys are needed:
   Key Type Description     RESTIC_PASSWORD Required Password that will be used to encrypt the backup snapshots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backend Overview | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/overview/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Stash Backends Stash supports various backends for storing data snapshots. It can be a cloud storage like GCS bucket, AWS S3, Azure Blob Storage etc. or a Kubernetes persistent volume like HostPath, PersistentVolumeClaim, NFS etc.
The following diagram shows how Stash sidecar container accesses and backs up data into a backend.
Fig: Stash Backend Overview  You have to create a Repository object which contains backend information and a Secret which contains necessary credentials to access the backend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GCS Backend | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/gcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/gcs/</guid>
      <description>Google Cloud Storage (GCS) Stash supports Google Cloud Storage(GCS) as a backend. This tutorial will show you how to use this backend.
In order to use Google Cloud Storage as backend, you have to create a Secret and a Repository object pointing to the desired GCS bucket.
 If the bucket already exists, the Google Cloud service account you provide to Stash only needs Storage Object Creator role permission. However, if the bucket does not exist, Stash will create the bucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Backend | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/local/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/local/</guid>
      <description>Local Backend Local backend refers to a local path inside stash sidecar container. Any Kubernetes supported persistent volume such as PersistentVolumeClaim, HostPath, EmptyDir (for testing only), NFS, gcePersistentDisk etc. can be used as local backend.
In order to use Kubernetes volumes as backend, you have to create a Secret and a Repository object pointing to the desired volume.
Create Storage Secret To configure storage secret for local backend, following secret keys are needed:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REST Backend | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/rest/</guid>
      <description>REST Backend Stash supports restic&amp;rsquo;s REST Server as a backend. This tutorial will show you how to use this backend.
In order to use REST Server as backend, you have to create a Secret and a Repository object pointing to the desired REST Server address.
Create Storage Secret To configure storage secret for this backend, following secret keys are needed:
   Key Type Description     RESTIC_PASSWORD Required Password that will be used to encrypt the backup snapshots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swift Backend | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/backends/swift/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack Swift Stash supports OpenStack Swift as a backend. This tutorial will show you how to use this backend.
In order to use OpenStack Swift as backend, you have to create a Secret and a Repository object pointing to the desired Swift container.
Create Storage Secret Stash supports Swift&amp;rsquo;s Keystone v1, v2, v3 authentication as well as token-based authentication.
Keystone v1 authentication:
For keystone v1 authentication, following secret keys are needed:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>