<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advance Use Cases | Stash on Kubernetes Anywhere — for Everybody</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/</link><description>Recent content in Advance Use Cases | Stash on Kubernetes Anywhere — for Everybody</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clone Data Volumes | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/clone-pvc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/clone-pvc/</guid><description>Clone Data Volumes using Stash Using Stash you can clone data volumes of a workload into a different namespace in a cluster. You can provide a template for PVC in RestoreSession. Stash will create PVCs according to the template, then it will restore data in that PVC. Then you can use the cloned PVCs to deploy your desired workload. This guide will show you how to clone backed up data into new PVCs using Stash.</description></item><item><title>File Ownership | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/ownership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/ownership/</guid><description>Handling Restored File Ownership in Stash Stash preserves permission bits of the restored files. However, it may change ownership (owner uid and gid) of the restored files in some cases. This tutorial will explain when and how ownership of the restored files can be changed. Then, we are going to explain how we can avoid or resolve this problem.
Understanding Backup and Restore Behaviour At first, let&amp;rsquo;s understand how backup and restore behaves in different scenario.</description></item><item><title>Instant Backup | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/instant-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/instant-backup/</guid><description>Instant Backup This guide will show you how to take an instant backup in Stash.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube.
Install Stash in your cluster following the steps here.
You should be familiar with the following Stash concepts:</description></item><item><title>Pause Backup | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/pause-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/guides/latest/advanced-use-case/pause-backup/</guid><description>Pause Backup Stash supports pausing backups without deleting respective BackupConfiguration. This guide will show you how to pause a scheduled backup in Stash.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube.
Install Stash in your cluster following the steps here.
You should be familiar with the following Stash concepts:</description></item></channel></rss>