<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FAQ | AppsCode on The Kubernetes Company</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FAQ | AppsCode on The Kubernetes Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Billing FAQ | AppsCode</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/billing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/billing/</guid>
      <description>What form of payments do you accept? You may purchase our products or upgrade your plan using an international credit card (Visa, MasterCard, American Express) and PayPal.
If I have multiple credit cards on file, which one do you charge? Our billing system will attempt to charge your primary credit card. If there is a specific card you&amp;rsquo;d like to use for payment, please make sure it is the primary credit card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal FAQ | AppsCode</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/legal/</guid>
      <description>What are the basic conditions for using AppsCode? In order to avail AppsCode services, you have to assure certain terms and conditions:
 You MUST be at least 13 years of age or beyond to use the Site and Services of AppsCode.
 You may not be allowed to use AppsCode Services you are a person barred from receiving the AppsCode Services under the laws of the United States or other countries, including the country in which you are resident or from which you use the AppsCode Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product FAQ | AppsCode</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/product/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/product/</guid>
      <description>How long is the Trial Period of AppsCode Paid Services? Do I have to register with a credit card from the very beginning? Trial Period for AppsCode paid services has a validity of fourteen (14) days. During this period you are not required to register with a credit card. In order to avoid service disruption you have to register with a valid credit card during the trial period.
Which Clouds are supported by AppsCode?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security &amp; Privacy FAQ | AppsCode</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/faq/security/</guid>
      <description>How do I report any security issues? If you find any vulnerabilities in AppsCode services, immediately report by email to security@appscode.com with the details of vulnerabilities arising. AppsCode appreciates working with bug reporter(s) to fix bug promptly. You can contact us securely using our PGP key found here.
Can AppsCode provide protection against Spoofing and Sniffing? Yes. AppsCode utilizes application isolation, operating system restrictions, and encrypted connections to further ensure risk is mitigated at all levels.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>