<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Platforms | Stash on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Platforms | Stash on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AKS | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/aks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/aks/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Using Stash with Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) This tutorial will show you how to use Stash to backup and restore a volume in Azure Kubernetes Service. Here, we are going to backup the /source/data folder of a busybox pod into Azure Blob Storage. Then, we are going to show how to recover this data into a PersistentVolumeClaim(PVC). We are going to also re-deploy deployment using this recovered volume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EKS | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/eks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/eks/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Using Stash with Amazon EKS This tutorial will show you how to use Stash to backup and restore a volume in Amazon Elastic Container Service for Kubernetes (EKS). Here, we are going to backup the /source/data folder of a busybox pod into AWS S3 bucket. Then, we are going to show how to recover this data into a PersistentVolumeClaim(PVC). We are going to also re-deploy deployment using this recovered volume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GKE | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/gke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/gke/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Using Stash with Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) This tutorial will show you how to use Stash to backup and restore a Kubernetes deployment in Google Kubernetes Engine. Here, we are going to back up the /source/data folder of a busybox pod into GCS bucket. Then, we are going to show how to recover this data into a gcePersistentDisk and PersistentVolumeClaim. We are going to also re-deploy deployment using this recovered volume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minio | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/minio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/minio/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Using Stash with TLS secured Minio Server Minio is an open source object storage server compatible with AWS S3 cloud storage service. This tutorial will show you how to use Stash to backup and restore a volume with a Minio backend. Here, we are going to backup the /source/data folder of a busybox pod into a Minio bucket. Then, we are going to show how to recover this data into a PersistentVolumeClaim(PVC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rook | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/rook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.0/guides/platforms/rook/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Using Stash with Rook Storage Service This tutorial will show you how to use Stash to backup and restore a Kubernetes volume in Rook storage service. Here, we are going to backup the /source/data folder of a busybox pod into AWS S3 compatible Rook Object Storage. Then, we are going to show how to recover this data into a PersistentVolumeClaim of Rook Block Storage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>