<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash/</guid>
      <description>stash Stash by AppsCode - Backup your Kubernetes Volumes
Synopsis Stash is a Kubernetes operator for restic. For more information, visit here: https://appscode.com/products/stash
Options  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) -h, --help help for stash --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files --stderrthreshold severity logs at or above this threshold go to stderr (default 2) -v, --v Level log level for V logs --vmodule moduleSpec comma-separated list of pattern=N settings for file-filtered logging  SEE ALSO  stash backup - Run Stash Backup stash check - Check restic backup stash recover - Recover restic backup stash run - Run Stash operator stash version - Prints binary version number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stash Backup</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_backup/</guid>
      <description>stash backup Run Stash Backup
Synopsis Run Stash Backup
stash backup [flags]  Options  --enable-rbac Enable RBAC -h, --help help for backup --image-tag string Check job image tag. --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --pushgateway-url string URL of Prometheus pushgateway used to cache backup metrics (default &amp;quot;http://stash-operator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stash Check</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_check/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_check/</guid>
      <description> stash check Check restic backup
Synopsis Check restic backup
stash check [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for check --host-name string Host name for workload. --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --restic-name string Name of the Restic CRD. --smart-prefix string Smart prefix for workload  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files --stderrthreshold severity logs at or above this threshold go to stderr (default 2) -v, --v Level log level for V logs --vmodule moduleSpec comma-separated list of pattern=N settings for file-filtered logging  SEE ALSO  stash - Stash by AppsCode - Backup your Kubernetes Volumes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stash Recover</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_recover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_recover/</guid>
      <description> stash recover Recover restic backup
Synopsis Recover restic backup
stash recover [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for recover --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --recovery-name string Name of the Recovery CRD.  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files --stderrthreshold severity logs at or above this threshold go to stderr (default 2) -v, --v Level log level for V logs --vmodule moduleSpec comma-separated list of pattern=N settings for file-filtered logging  SEE ALSO  stash - Stash by AppsCode - Backup your Kubernetes Volumes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stash Run</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_run/</guid>
      <description>stash run Run Stash operator
Synopsis Run Stash operator
stash run [flags]  Options  --address string Address to listen on for web interface and telemetry. (default &amp;quot;:56790&amp;quot;) -h, --help help for run --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --rbac Enable RBAC for operator --resync-period duration If non-zero, will re-list this often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stash Version</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.2/reference/stash_version/</guid>
      <description> stash version Prints binary version number.
Synopsis Prints binary version number.
stash version [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for version  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files --stderrthreshold severity logs at or above this threshold go to stderr (default 2) -v, --v Level log level for V logs --vmodule moduleSpec comma-separated list of pattern=N settings for file-filtered logging  SEE ALSO  stash - Stash by AppsCode - Backup your Kubernetes Volumes  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>