<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Certificate on The Kubernetes Company</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/voyager/8.0.1/guides/certificate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Certificate on The Kubernetes Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/voyager/8.0.1/guides/certificate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Certificate FAQ | Voyager</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/voyager/8.0.1/guides/certificate/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/voyager/8.0.1/guides/certificate/faq/</guid>
      <description>New to Voyager? Please start here.
 FAQ Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt FAQs How do I renew my LE certificates? LE issues certificates that are valid for 90 days. Voyager operator will try renewing your certificate 7 days prior to expiration. Once renewed certificates are issued, HAProxy will be automatically updated to use the new certificates.
I think I did everything according to this doc but my certificate is not issuing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certificate | Voyager</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/voyager/8.0.1/guides/certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/voyager/8.0.1/guides/certificate/</guid>
      <description> Guides Guides show you how to use Voyager&amp;rsquo;s built-in certificate manager to issue free TLS/SSL certificates from Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt.
Features  Provision free TLS certificates (including wildcard certificates) from Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt. Manage certificates declaratively using a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definition (CRD). Domain validation using ACME http-01 and dns-01 challenges. Support for many popular DNS providers. Auto Renew certificates. Use issued certificates with Ingress to secure communications.  Next Steps  Issue Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt certificate using HTTP-01 challenge DNS-01 chanllege providers  Issue Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt certificate using AWS Route53 Issue Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt certificate using Google Cloud DNS Supported DNS Challenge Providers  Deleting Certificate Frequently Asked Questions  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete Certificate | Voyager</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/voyager/8.0.1/guides/certificate/delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/voyager/8.0.1/guides/certificate/delete/</guid>
      <description>New to Voyager? Please start here.
 Deleting Certificate Pausing Certificte Voyager operator periodically (default 5 mins) checks each certificate whether whether it needs to be reissued. If you have a bad configuration (example, bad dns credentials), this can led to rate limit issued with Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt. You can delete the certificate object to stop retries. Alternatively, you can mark the certificate object as spec.paused: true. This will cause Voyager operator to skip checking this certificate for renewals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>