<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guides | Stash on The Kubernetes Company</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guides | Stash on The Kubernetes Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup Volumes | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/backup/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Backup Volumes using Stash This tutorial will show you how to use Stash to back up a Kubernetes volume. Here, we are going to backup the /source/data folder of a busybox pod into an NFS volume. NFS volume is configured as a Local backend of Stash.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offline Backup | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/offline_backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/offline_backup/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Offline Backup This tutorial will show you how to backup a Kubernetes deployment using Stash in offline mode. By default, stash takes backup in online mode where sidecar container is added to take periodic backups and check backups. But sometimes you need to ensure that source data is not being modified while taking the backup, that means running backup while keeping workload pod stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBAC | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/rbac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/rbac/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Configuring RBAC To use Stash in a RBAC enabled cluster, install Stash with RBAC options. This creates a ClusterRole named stash-sidecar.
Sidecar container added to workloads makes various calls to Kubernetes api. ServiceAccounts used with Deployment, ReplicaSet, DaemonSet and ReplicationController workloads are automatically bound to stash-sidecar ClusterRole by Stash operator. Users should manually add the following RoleBinding to service accounts used with StatefulSet workloads to authorize these api calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restore Volumes | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/restore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/restore/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Restore from Backup This tutorial will show you how to restore backed up volume using Stash. Here, we are going to recover backed up data into a PVC. Then, we are going to re-deploy the workload using the recovered volume.
Before You Begin To proceed with this tutorial, you have to meet following requirements:
 At first, you need to have some backup taken by Stash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Table of Contents | Guides</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/</guid>
      <description>Guides Guides show you how to perform tasks with Stash.
 Learn how to use Stash to backup a Kubernetes deployment here. To restore a backup see here. To run backup in offline mode see here See the list of supported backends and how to configure them here. Learn to use Stash in Google Kubernetes Engine here Learn to use Stash with self-hosted TLS secured Minio Server here. Learn to use Stash in Rook Storage System here See working examples for supported workload types here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workloads | Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/workloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.8.3/guides/workloads/</guid>
      <description>New to Stash? Please start here.
 Supported Workloads Stash supports the following types of Kubernetes workloads.
Deployments To backup a Deployment, create a Restic with matching selectors. You can find a full working demo in examples folder.
ReplicaSets To backup a ReplicaSet, create a Restic with matching selectors. You can find a full working demo in examples folder.
ReplicationControllers To backup a ReplicationController, create a Restic with matching selectors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>