<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configuration Syncer | Kubernetes on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/kubed/0.5.0/guides/config-syncer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configuration Syncer | Kubernetes on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/kubed/0.5.0/guides/config-syncer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration Syncer | Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/kubed/0.5.0/guides/config-syncer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/kubed/0.5.0/guides/config-syncer/</guid>
      <description> Configuration Syncer This section contains guides on how to use Kubed to synchronize Configmaps or Secrets across namespaces of a Kubernetes Cluster or across Kubernetes clusters.
 Synchronize Configuration across Namespaces: This tutorial will show you how Kubed can sync ConfigMaps/Secrets across Kubernetes namespaces. Synchronize Configuration across Clusters: This tutorial will show you how Kubed can sync ConfigMaps/Secrets across Kubernetes cluster.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Synchronize Configuration across Kubernetes Clusters</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/kubed/0.5.0/guides/config-syncer/inter-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/kubed/0.5.0/guides/config-syncer/inter-cluster/</guid>
      <description>New to Kubed? Please start here.
 Synchronize Configuration across Clusters You can synchronize a ConfigMap or a Secret into different clusters using Kubed. For this you need to provide a kube-config file consisting cluster contexts and specify context names in comma separated format using kubed.appscode.com/sync-contexts annotation. Kubed will create a copy of that ConfigMap/Secret in all clusters specified by the annotation. For each cluster, it will sync into source namespace by default, but if namespace specified in the context (in the kube-config file), it will sync into that namespace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Synchronize Configuration across Namespaces</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/kubed/0.5.0/guides/config-syncer/intra-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/kubed/0.5.0/guides/config-syncer/intra-cluster/</guid>
      <description>New to Kubed? Please start here.
 Synchronize Configuration across Namespaces Say, you are using some Docker private registry. You want to keep its image pull secret synchronized across all namespaces of a Kubernetes cluster. Kubed can do that for you. If a ConfigMap or a Secret has the annotation kubed.appscode.com/sync: &amp;quot;&amp;quot;, Kubed will create a copy of that ConfigMap/Secret in all existing namespaces. Kubed will also create this ConfigMap/Secret, when you create a new namespace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>