<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stash Operator on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stash Operator on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_backup/</guid>
      <description>stash backup Run Stash Backup
Synopsis Run Stash Backup
stash backup [flags]  Options  --burst int The maximum burst for throttle (default 100) --docker-registry string Check job image registry. (default &amp;quot;appscode&amp;quot;) -h, --help help for backup --image-tag string Check job image tag. --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --pushgateway-url string URL of Prometheus pushgateway used to cache backup metrics --qps float The maximum QPS to the master from this client (default 100) --restic-name string Name of the Restic used as configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup-Pvc</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_backup-pvc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_backup-pvc/</guid>
      <description>stash backup-pvc Takes a backup of Persistent Volume Claim
Synopsis Takes a backup of Persistent Volume Claim
stash backup-pvc [flags]  Options  --backup-dirs strings List of directories to be backed up --bucket string Name of the cloud bucket/container (keep empty for local backend) --enable-cache Specify whether to enable caching for restic --endpoint string Endpoint for s3/s3 compatible backend -h, --help help for backup-pvc --hostname string Name of the host machine (default &amp;quot;host-0&amp;quot;) --max-connections int Specify maximum concurrent connections for GCS, Azure and B2 backend --metrics-dir string Directory where to write metric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_check/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_check/</guid>
      <description>stash check Check restic backup
Synopsis Check restic backup
stash check [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for check --host-name string Host name for workload. --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --restic-name string Name of the Restic CRD. --smart-prefix string Smart prefix for workload  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --enable-status-subresource If true, uses sub resource for crds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create-Backupsession</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_create-backupsession/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_create-backupsession/</guid>
      <description>stash create-backupsession create a BackupSession
Synopsis create a BackupSession
stash create-backupsession [flags]  Options  --backupsession.name string Set BackupSession Name --backupsession.namespace string Set BackupSession Namespace (default &amp;quot;default&amp;quot;) -h, --help help for create-backupsession --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig)  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --enable-status-subresource If true, uses sub resource for crds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create-Vs</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_create-vs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_create-vs/</guid>
      <description>stash create-vs Take snapshot of PersistentVolumeClaims
Synopsis Take snapshot of PersistentVolumeClaims
stash create-vs [flags]  Options  --backupsession.name string Set BackupSession Name -h, --help help for create-vs --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --metrics-enabled Specify whether to export Prometheus metrics --pushgateway-url string Pushgateway URL where the metrics will be pushed  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --enable-status-subresource If true, uses sub resource for crds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_forget/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_forget/</guid>
      <description>stash forget Delete snapshots from a restic repository
Synopsis Delete snapshots from a restic repository
stash forget [snapshotID ...] [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for forget --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --repo-name string Name of the Repository CRD.  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --enable-status-subresource If true, uses sub resource for crds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recover</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_recover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_recover/</guid>
      <description>stash recover Recover restic backup
Synopsis Recover restic backup
stash recover [flags]  Options  --backoff-max-wait duration Maximum wait for initial response from kube apiserver; 0 disables the timeout -h, --help help for recover --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --recovery-name string Name of the Recovery CRD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restore</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_restore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_restore/</guid>
      <description>stash restore Restore from backup
Synopsis Restore from backup
stash restore [flags]  Options  --backoff-max-wait duration Maximum wait for initial response from kube apiserver; 0 disables the timeout --enable-cache Specify whether to enable caching for restic (default true) -h, --help help for restore --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --max-connections int Specify maximum concurrent connections for GCS, Azure and B2 backend --metrics-enabled Specify whether to export Prometheus metrics --pushgateway-url string Pushgateway URL where the metrics will be pushed --restore-model string Specify whether using job or init-container to restore (default init-container) (default &amp;quot;init-container&amp;quot;) --restore-session string Name of the RestoreSession CRD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restore-Pvc</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_restore-pvc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_restore-pvc/</guid>
      <description>stash restore-pvc Takes a restore of Persistent Volume Claim
Synopsis Takes a restore of Persistent Volume Claim
stash restore-pvc [flags]  Options  --bucket string Name of the cloud bucket/container (keep empty for local backend) --enable-cache Specify whether to enable caching for restic --endpoint string Endpoint for s3/s3 compatible backend -h, --help help for restore-pvc --hostname string Name of the host machine (default &amp;quot;host-0&amp;quot;) --max-connections int Specify maximum concurrent connections for GCS, Azure and B2 backend --metrics-dir string Directory where to write metric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restore-Vs</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_restore-vs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_restore-vs/</guid>
      <description>stash restore-vs Restore PVC from VolumeSnapshot
Synopsis Restore PVC from VolumeSnapshot
stash restore-vs [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for restore-vs --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --metrics-enabled Specify whether to export Prometheus metrics --pushgateway-url string Pushgateway URL where the metrics will be pushed --restoresession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_run/</guid>
      <description>stash run Launch Stash Controller
Synopsis Launch Stash Controller
stash run [flags]  Options  --audit-dynamic-configuration Enables dynamic audit configuration. This feature also requires the DynamicAuditing feature flag --audit-log-batch-buffer-size int The size of the buffer to store events before batching and writing. Only used in batch mode. (default 10000) --audit-log-batch-max-size int The maximum size of a batch. Only used in batch mode. (default 1) --audit-log-batch-max-wait duration The amount of time to wait before force writing the batch that hadn&#39;t reached the max size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run-Backup</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_run-backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_run-backup/</guid>
      <description>stash run-backup Take backup of workload directories
Synopsis Take backup of workload directories
stash run-backup [flags]  Options  --backup-configuration string Set BackupConfiguration Name --enable-cache Specify whether to enable caching for restic (default true) -h, --help help for run-backup --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --max-connections int Specify maximum concurrent connections for GCS, Azure and B2 backend --metrics-enabled Specify whether to export Prometheus metrics --pushgateway-url string URL of Prometheus pushgateway used to cache backup metrics --secret-dir string Directory where storage secret has been mounted  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --enable-status-subresource If true, uses sub resource for crds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaledown</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_scaledown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_scaledown/</guid>
      <description>stash scaledown Scale down workload
Synopsis Scale down workload
stash scaledown [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for scaledown --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --selector string Label used to select Restic&#39;s workload  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --enable-status-subresource If true, uses sub resource for crds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapshots</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_snapshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_snapshots/</guid>
      <description>stash snapshots Get snapshots of restic repo
Synopsis Get snapshots of restic repo
stash snapshots [snapshotID ...] [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for snapshots --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --repo-name string Name of the Repository CRD.  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --enable-status-subresource If true, uses sub resource for crds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stash</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/</guid>
      <description>stash Stash by AppsCode - Backup your Kubernetes Volumes
Synopsis Stash is a Kubernetes operator for restic. For more information, visit here: https://appscode.com/products/stash
Options  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --enable-status-subresource If true, uses sub resource for crds. -h, --help help for stash --log-flush-frequency duration Maximum number of seconds between log flushes (default 5s) --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files (default true) --service-name string Stash service name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update-Status</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_update-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_update-status/</guid>
      <description>stash update-status Update status of Repository, Backup/Restore Session
Synopsis Update status of Repository, Backup/Restore Session
stash update-status [flags]  Options  --backup-session string Name of the Backup Session -h, --help help for update-status --kubeconfig string Path to kubeconfig file with authorization information (the master location is set by the master flag). --master string The address of the Kubernetes API server (overrides any value in kubeconfig) --namespace string Namespace of Backup/Restore Session (default &amp;quot;default&amp;quot;) --output-dir string Directory where output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/reference/operator/stash_version/</guid>
      <description>stash version Prints binary version number.
Synopsis Prints binary version number.
stash version [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for version --short Print just the version number.  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --bypass-validating-webhook-xray if true, bypasses validating webhook xray checks --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --enable-status-subresource If true, uses sub resource for crds. --log-flush-frequency duration Maximum number of seconds between log flushes (default 5s) --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files (default true) --service-name string Stash service name.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>