<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Incident on The Kubernetes Company</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/7.0.0/concepts/incident/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Incident on The Kubernetes Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/7.0.0/concepts/incident/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Acknowledgement Concepts</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/7.0.0/concepts/incident/acknowledgement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/7.0.0/concepts/incident/acknowledgement/</guid>
      <description>Acknowledgement Kubernetes Extended Api Server resource Acknowledgement is used to acknowledge an Incident with type Problem.
Following is the example of Acknowledgement object
apiVersion: incidents.monitoring.appscode.com kind: Acknowledgement metadata: name: cluster.pod-exists-demo-0.20180428-1109 namespace: demo request: comment: working on fix  When user creates this Acknowledgement object, Searchlight operator gets Incident with same name of Acknowledgement object. Operator then acknowledges Icinga notification with provided comment.
To remove acknowledgement, you just need to delete Acknowledgement object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incident Concepts</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/7.0.0/concepts/incident/incident/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/7.0.0/concepts/incident/incident/</guid>
      <description>Incident What is Incident A Incident is a Kubernetes Custom Resource Definition (CRD). It provides information on notifications sent by Searchlight for alerts.
Incident Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, a Incident has apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields. It also has a .spec section.
Below is an example Incident object maintained by Searchlight.
apiVersion: monitoring.appscode.com/v1alpha1 kind: Incident metadata: name: cluster.pod-exists-demo-0.20180428-1109 namespace: demo labels: monitoring.appscode.com/alert: pod-exists-demo-0 monitoring.appscode.com/alert-type: cluster monitoring.appscode.com/recovered: true status: lastNotificationType: Recovery notifications: - type: Problem checkOutput: Found 10 pod(s) instead of 11 author: searchlight-user firstTimestamp: 20180428-1109 lastTimestamp: 20180428-1119 state: Critical - type: Acknowledgement checkOutput: Found 10 pod(s) instead of 11 author: admin comment: working on fix firstTimestamp: 20180428-1142 lastTimestamp: 20180428-1142 state: Critical - type: Recovery checkOutput: Found all pods author: searchlight-user firstTimestamp: 20180428-1237 lastTimestamp: 20180428-1237 state: Ok  Here,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>