<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cluster Alert on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cluster Alert on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CA Cert</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/ca-cert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/ca-cert/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check ca-cert Check command ca-cert checks the expiration timestamp of Kubernetes api server CA certificate. No longer you have to get a surprise that the CA certificate for your cluster has expired.
Spec ca-cert check command has the following variables:
 warning - Condition for warning, compare with tiem left before expiration. (Default: TTL &amp;lt; 360h) critical - Condition for critical, compare with tiem left before expiration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cert</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/cert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/cert/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check cert Check command cert checks the expiration timestamp of any certificate from Secrets. No longer you have to get a surprise that your certificates have expired.
Spec cert check command has the following variables:
 selector - Selector (label query) to filter on, supports &amp;lsquo;=&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;==&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;!=&amp;rsquo; secretName - Name of secret from where certificates are checked secretKey - Name of secret key where certificates are kept warning - Remaining duration for Warning state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Component Status</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/component-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/component-status/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check component-status Check command component-status is used to check status of Kubernetes components. Returns OK if components are Healthy, otherwise, returns Critical.
Spec component-status has the following variables:
 selector - Label selector for components whose existence are checked. componentName - Name of Kubernetes component whose existence is checked.  Execution of this command can result in following states:
 OK Critical Unknown  Tutorial Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/event/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check event Check command event is used to check Kubernetes events. This plugin checks for all Warning events happened in the last spec.checkInterval duration.
Spec event check command has the following variables:
 clockSkew - Clock skew in Duration. [Default: 30s]. This time is added with spec.checkInterval while checking events involvedObjectKind - Kind of involved object used to select events involvedObjectName - Name of involved object used to select events involvedObjectNamespace - Namespace of involved object used to select events involvedObjectUID - UID of involved object used to select events  Execution of this command can result in following states:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON Path</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/json-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/json-path/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check json-path Check command json-path is used to check JSON HTTP response using jsonpath queries.
Spec json-path check command has the following variables:
 url - URL to get data secretName - Name of Kubernetes Secret used to call HTTP api. warning - Query for warning which returns [true/false]. critical - Query for critical which returns [true/false].  Query A query used in warning and critical variable must return boolean [true/false].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node Exists</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/node-exists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/node-exists/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check node-exists Check command node-exists is used to check existence of nodes in a Kubernetes cluster.
Spec node-exists has the following variables:
 selector - Label selector for nodes whose existence are checked. nodeName - Name of Kubernetes node whose existence is checked. count - Number of expected Kubernetes nodes  Execution of this command can result in following states:
 OK Critical Unknown  Tutorial Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pod Exists</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/pod-exists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0/guides/cluster-alerts/pod-exists/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check pod-exists Check command pod-exists is used to check existence of pods in a Kubernetes cluster.
Spec pod-exists has the following variables:
 selector - Label selector for pods whose existence are checked. podName - Name of Kubernetes pod whose existence is checked. count - Number of expected Kubernetes pods  Execution of this command can result in following states:
 OK Critical Unknown  Tutorial Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>