<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs | Kubed on GitHub for Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs | Kubed on GitHub for Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog | Kubed</title>
      <link>https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/welcome/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/welcome/changelog/</guid>
      <description>Change Log v0.12.0-rc.2 (2020-01-10) Full Changelog
Merged pull requests:
 Permit kubed to write events #379 (tamalsaha)  v0.12.0-rc.1 (2020-01-10) Full Changelog
Closed issues:
 Kubernetes 1.16 and &amp;ldquo;extensions/v1beta1&amp;rdquo; #369 Project roadmap #363 kubed is messing up api-resources #351 Don&amp;rsquo;t regenerate a certificate authority and a certificate everytime you deploy the helm chart #346 liveness check does not detect when kubed is not responding to API requests anymore #343 kube-controller-manager errors #340 Performance optimizing syncer #335 How to properly restore snapshot #303 Use audit policy server to forward events #194 Auto mount image pull secret for docker registry #191 Need automatic clean up of backed up yamls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing | Kubed</title>
      <link>https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/welcome/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/welcome/contributing/</guid>
      <description>Contribution Guidelines Want to hack on Kubed?
AppsCode projects are Apache 2.0 licensed and accept contributions via GitHub pull requests. This document outlines some of the conventions on development workflow, commit message formatting, contact points and other resources to make it easier to get your contribution accepted.
Certificate of Origin By contributing to this project you agree to the Developer Certificate of Origin (DCO). This document was created by the Linux Kernel community and is a simple statement that you, as a contributor, have the legal right to make the contribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support | Kubed</title>
      <link>https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/welcome/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/welcome/support/</guid>
      <description>Support We use Slack for public discussions. To chit chat with us or the rest of the community, join us in the AppsCode Slack team channel #kubed. To sign up, use our Slack inviter.
If you have found a bug with Kubed or want to request for new features, please file an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weclome | Kubed</title>
      <link>https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode.com/products/kubed/v0.12.0-rc.2/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Kubed Kubed (pronounced Cube-Dee) by AppsCode is a Kubernetes Cluster Operator Daemon. From here you can learn all about Kubed&amp;rsquo;s architecture and how to deploy and use Kubed.
  Concepts. Concepts explain some significant aspect of Kubed. This is where you can learn about what Kubed does and how it does it.
  Setup. Setup contains instructions for installing the Kubed in various cloud providers.
  Guides. Guides show you how to perform tasks with Kubed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>