<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/swift/0.7.1/reference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/swift/0.7.1/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Swift</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/swift/0.7.1/reference/swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/swift/0.7.1/reference/swift/</guid>
      <description>swift Swift by Appscode - Ajax friendly Helm Tiller Proxy
Synopsis Swift by Appscode - Ajax friendly Helm Tiller Proxy
Options  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) -h, --help help for swift --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files --stderrthreshold severity logs at or above this threshold go to stderr (default 2) -v, --v Level log level for V logs --vmodule moduleSpec comma-separated list of pattern=N settings for file-filtered logging  SEE ALSO  swift run - Run swift apis swift version - Prints binary version number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swift Run</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/swift/0.7.1/reference/swift_run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/swift/0.7.1/reference/swift_run/</guid>
      <description>swift run Run swift apis
Synopsis Run swift apis
swift run [flags]  Options  --api-domain string Domain used to server swift api --cacert-file string File containing CA certificate --cert-file string File container server TLS certificate --connector string Name of connector used to connect to Tiller server. Valid values are: incluster, direct, kubeconfig, appscode --cors-origin-allow-subdomain Allow CORS request from subdomains of origin --cors-origin-host string Allowed CORS origin host e.g, domain[:port] --enable-cors Enable CORS support -h, --help help for run --key-file string File containing server TLS private key --kube-context string Kube context used by &#39;kubeconfig&#39; connection --ops-addr string Address to listen on for web interface and telemetry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swift Version</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/swift/0.7.1/reference/swift_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/swift/0.7.1/reference/swift_version/</guid>
      <description> swift version Prints binary version number.
Synopsis Prints binary version number.
swift version [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for version  Options inherited from parent commands  --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --log_backtrace_at traceLocation when logging hits line file:N, emit a stack trace (default :0) --log_dir string If non-empty, write log files in this directory --logtostderr log to standard error instead of files --stderrthreshold severity logs at or above this threshold go to stderr (default 2) -v, --v Level log level for V logs --vmodule moduleSpec comma-separated list of pattern=N settings for file-filtered logging  SEE ALSO  swift - Swift by Appscode - Ajax friendly Helm Tiller Proxy  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>