<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs | Guard on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs | Guard on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog | Guard</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/welcome/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/welcome/changelog/</guid>
      <description>Change Log 0.3.0 (2018-12-03) Full Changelog
Fixed bugs:
 Fix panic if there is no $HOME/.kube/config #179 (nightfury1204)  Closed issues:
 Github connector docs asks for unnecessary public_repo permissions #195 Guard should not log password/secrets #194 Issues with LDAP and guard get installer #193 Dependabot couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a Gopkg.toml for this project #191 Guard crashes multiple times a day #190 Missing binaries for 0.2.1 guard-darwin #189 Guard pod keeps restarting ~ every 8 hours #187 Logo Proposal for Guard #184 Using Gitlab&amp;rsquo;s full_path instead of name while using authentication by Groups #181 panic: assignment to entry in nil map #178  Merged pull requests:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing | Guard</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/welcome/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/welcome/contributing/</guid>
      <description>Contribution Guidelines Want to hack on Guard?
AppsCode projects are Apache 2.0 licensed and accept contributions via GitHub pull requests. This document outlines some of the conventions on development workflow, commit message formatting, contact points and other resources to make it easier to get your contribution accepted.
Certificate of Origin By contributing to this project you agree to the Developer Certificate of Origin (DCO). This document was created by the Linux Kernel community and is a simple statement that you, as a contributor, have the legal right to make the contribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support | Guard</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/welcome/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/welcome/support/</guid>
      <description>Support We use Slack for public discussions. To chit chat with us or the rest of the community, join us in the AppsCode Slack team channel #guard. To sign up, use our Slack inviter.
If you have found a bug with Searchlight or want to request for new features, please file an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome | Guard</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/guard/0.3.0/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Guard Guard by AppsCode is a Kubernetes Webhook Authentication server. Using guard, you can log into your Kubernetes cluster using a Github or Google authentication token. Guard also sets authenticated user&amp;rsquo;s groups to their Github teams or Google groups. This allows cluster administrators to setup RBAC rules based on membership in Github teams or Google groups.
From here you can learn all about Guard&amp;rsquo;s architecture and how to deploy and use Guard.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>