<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guides | Stash on Kubernetes Anywhere — for Everybody</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/</link><description>Recent content in Guides | Stash on Kubernetes Anywhere — for Everybody</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Backup Volumes | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/backup/</guid><description>New to Stash? Please start here.
Backup This tutorial will show you how to use Stash to backup a Kubernetes deployment. At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster. If you do not already have a cluster, you can create one by using Minikube. Now, install Stash in your cluster following the steps here.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/monitoring/</guid><description>New to Stash? Please start here.
Monitoring Stash Stash has native support for monitoring via Prometheus.
Monitoring Stash Operator Stash operator exposes Prometheus native monitoring data via /metrics endpoint on :56790 port. You can setup a CoreOS Prometheus ServiceMonitor using stash-operator service.
Monitoring Backup Operation Since backup operations are run as cron jobs, Stash can use Prometheus Pushgateway cache metrics for backup operation. The installation scripts for Stash operator deploys a Prometheus Pushgateway as a sidecar container.</description></item><item><title>Offline Backup | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/offline_backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/offline_backup/</guid><description>New to Stash? Please start here.
Offline Backup This tutorial will show you how to backup a Kubernetes deployment using Stash in offline mode. By default, stash takes backup in online mode where sidecar container is added to take periodic backups and check backups. But sometimes you need to ensure that source data is not being modified while taking backup, that means running backup while keeping workload pod stopped.</description></item><item><title>RBAC | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/rbac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/rbac/</guid><description>New to Stash? Please start here.
Configuring RBAC To use Stash in a RBAC enabled cluster, install Stash with RBAC options. This creates a ClusterRole named stash-sidecar.
Sidecar container added to workloads makes various calls to Kubernetes api. ServiceAccounts used with Deployment, ReplicaSet, DaemonSet and ReplicationController workloads are automatically bound to stash-sidecar ClusterRole by Stash operator. Users should manually add the following RoleBinding to service accounts used with StatefulSet workloads to authorize these api calls.</description></item><item><title>Restore Volumes | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/restore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/restore/</guid><description>New to Stash? Please start here.
Restore Backup This tutorial will show you how to restore a Stash backup. At first, backup a kubernetes workload volume by following the steps here.
To restore a backup, you need to create a Recovery CRD by specifying Restic, target workload and volume where backup will be restored.
$ kubectl apply -f ./docs/examples/tutorial/recovery.yaml recovery &amp;quot;stash-demo&amp;quot; created apiVersion: stash.appscode.com/v1alpha1 kind: Recovery metadata: name: stash-demo namespace: default spec: workload: kind: Deployment name: stash-demo backend: local: mountPath: /safe/data hostPath: path: /data/stash-test/restic-repo storageSecretName: stash-demo paths: - /source/data recoveredVolumes: - mountPath: /source/data hostPath: path: /data/stash-test/restic-restored Here,</description></item><item><title>Supported Backends | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/backends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/backends/</guid><description>New to Stash? Please start here.
Stash Backends Backend is where restic stores snapshots. For any backend, a Kubernetes Secret in the same namespace is needed to provide restic repository credentials. This Secret can be configured by setting spec.backend.storageSecretName field. This document lists the various supported backends for Stash and how to configure those.
Local Local backend refers to a local path inside stash sidecar container. Any Kubernetes supported persistent volume can be used here.</description></item><item><title>Table of Contents | Guides</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/</guid><description>Guides Guides show you how to perform tasks with Stash.
Learn how to use Stash to backup a Kubernetes deployment here. To restore a backup see here. To run backup in offline mode see here See the list of supported backends and how to configure them here. See working examples for supported workload types here. Thinking about monitoring your backup operations? Stash works out-of-the-box with Prometheus. Learn about how to configure RBAC roles.</description></item><item><title>Workload Initializer | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/initializer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/initializer/</guid><description>New to Stash? Please start here.
Workload Initializer Stash operator can be used as a workload initializer. For this you need to create a InitializerConfiguration with initializer named stash.appscode.com. Please note that, this uses an alpha feature of Kubernetes.
$ kubectl apply -f ./hack/deploy/initializer.yaml initializerconfiguration &amp;quot;stash-initializer-config&amp;quot; created apiVersion: admissionregistration.k8s.io/v1alpha1 kind: InitializerConfiguration metadata: labels: app: stash name: stash-initializer initializers: - name: stash.appscode.com rules: - apiGroups: - &amp;quot;*&amp;quot; apiVersions: - &amp;quot;*&amp;quot; resources: - daemonsets - deployments - replicasets - replicationcontrollers - statefulsets This is helpful when you create Restic before creating workload objects.</description></item><item><title>Workloads | Stash</title><link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/workloads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/0.6.3/guides/workloads/</guid><description>New to Stash? Please start here.
Supported Workloads Stash supports the following types of Kubernetes workloads.
Deployments To backup a Deployment, create a Restic with matching selectors. You can find a full working demo in examples folder.
ReplicaSets To backup a ReplicaSet, create a Restic with matching selectors. You can find a full working demo in examples folder.
ReplicationControllers To backup a ReplicationController, create a Restic with matching selectors.</description></item></channel></rss>