<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pod Alert on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0-rc.0/guides/pod-alerts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pod Alert on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0-rc.0/guides/pod-alerts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pod Exec</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0-rc.0/guides/pod-alerts/pod-exec/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0-rc.0/guides/pod-alerts/pod-exec/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check pod-exec Check command pod-exec is used to check status of a command run inside Kubernetes pods. Returns OK if exit code is zero, otherwise, returns Critical.
Spec pod-exec check command has the following variables:
 container - Container name in a Kubernetes Pod cmd - Exec command. [Default: &amp;lsquo;/bin/sh&amp;rsquo;] argv - Exec command arguments. [Format: &amp;lsquo;arg; arg; arg&amp;rsquo;]  Execution of this command can result in following states:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pod Status</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0-rc.0/guides/pod-alerts/pod-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0-rc.0/guides/pod-alerts/pod-status/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check pod-status Check command pod-status is used to check status of Kubernetes pods. Returns OK if status.phase of a pod is Succeeded or Running, otherwise, returns Critical.
Spec pod-status check command has no variables. Execution of this command can result in following states:
 OK Critical Unknown  Tutorial Before You Begin At first, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster, and the kubectl command-line tool must be configured to communicate with your cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pod Volume</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0-rc.0/guides/pod-alerts/pod-volume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/searchlight/8.0.0-rc.0/guides/pod-alerts/pod-volume/</guid>
      <description>New to Searchlight? Please start here.
 Check pod-volume Check command pod-volume is used to check percentage of available space in Kubernetes Pods.
Spec pod-volume check command has the following variables:
 volumeName - Name of volume whose usage stats will be checked secretName - Name of Kubernetes Secret used to pass hostfacts auth info warning - Warning level value (usage percentage defaults to 80.0) critical - Critical level value (usage percentage defaults to 95.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>