<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stash kubectl plugin on GitHub for Kubernetes</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/</link><description>Recent content in Stash kubectl plugin on GitHub for Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clone</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_clone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_clone/</guid><description>kubectl-stash clone Clone Kubernetes resources
Synopsis Clone Kubernetes resources
Options -h, --help help for clone --to-namespace string Destination namespace. Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/tamal/.kube/http-cache&amp;quot;) --certificate-authority string Path to a cert file for the certificate authority --client-certificate string Path to a client certificate file for TLS --client-key string Path to a client key file for TLS --cluster string The name of the kubeconfig cluster to use --context string The name of the kubeconfig context to use --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --insecure-skip-tls-verify If true, the server&#39;s certificate will not be checked for validity.</description></item><item><title>Clone Pvc</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_clone_pvc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_clone_pvc/</guid><description>kubectl-stash clone pvc Clone PVC
Synopsis Use Backup and Restore process for cloning PVC
kubectl-stash clone pvc [flags] Examples # Clone PVC stash clone pvc source-pvc -n demo --to-namespace=demo1 --secret=&amp;lt;secret&amp;gt; --bucket=&amp;lt;bucket&amp;gt; --prefix=&amp;lt;prefix&amp;gt; --provider=&amp;lt;provider&amp;gt; Options --bucket string Name of the cloud bucket/container --endpoint string Endpoint for s3/s3 compatible backend -h, --help help for pvc --max-connections int Specify maximum concurrent connections for GCS, Azure and B2 backend --prefix string Prefix denotes the directory inside the backend --provider string Backend provider (i.</description></item><item><title>Cp</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp/</guid><description>kubectl-stash cp Copy stash resources from one namespace to another namespace
Synopsis Copy stash resources from one namespace to another namespace
Options -h, --help help for cp --to-namespace string Destination namespace. Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups.</description></item><item><title>Cp Backupconfig</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp_backupconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp_backupconfig/</guid><description>kubectl-stash cp backupconfig Copy BackupConfiguration from one namespace to another namespace
Synopsis Copy BackupConfiguration with respective Repository and Secret if they are not present in the target namespace
kubectl-stash cp backupconfig [flags] Options -h, --help help for backupconfig Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups.</description></item><item><title>Cp Repository</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp_repository/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp_repository/</guid><description>kubectl-stash cp repository Copy Repository and Secret
Synopsis Copy Repository and Secret from one namespace to another namespace
kubectl-stash cp repository [flags] Options -h, --help help for repository Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups.</description></item><item><title>Cp Secret</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp_secret/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp_secret/</guid><description>kubectl-stash cp secret Copy Secret
Synopsis Copy Secret from one namespace to another namespace
kubectl-stash cp secret [flags] Options -h, --help help for secret Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/tamal/.</description></item><item><title>Cp Volumesnapshot</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp_volumesnapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_cp_volumesnapshot/</guid><description>kubectl-stash cp volumesnapshot Copy VolumeSnapshot
Synopsis Copy VolumeSnapshot from one namespace to another namespace
kubectl-stash cp volumesnapshot [flags] Options -h, --help help for volumesnapshot Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/tamal/.</description></item><item><title>Create</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_create/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_create/</guid><description>kubectl-stash create create stash resources
Synopsis create stash resources
Options -h, --help help for create Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/tamal/.kube/http-cache&amp;quot;) --certificate-authority string Path to a cert file for the certificate authority --client-certificate string Path to a client certificate file for TLS --client-key string Path to a client key file for TLS --cluster string The name of the kubeconfig cluster to use --context string The name of the kubeconfig context to use --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --insecure-skip-tls-verify If true, the server&#39;s certificate will not be checked for validity.</description></item><item><title>Create Backupconfig</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_create_backupconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_create_backupconfig/</guid><description>kubectl-stash create backupconfig Create a new BackupConfiguration
Synopsis Create a new BackupConfiguration to backup a target
kubectl-stash create backupconfig [flags] Examples # Create a new BackupConfiguration # stash create backupconfig --namespace=&amp;lt;namespace&amp;gt; gcs-repo [Flag] # For Restic driver stash create backupconfig ss-backup --namespace=demo --repository=gcs-repo --schedule=&amp;quot;*/4 * * * *&amp;quot; --target-apiversion=apps/v1 --target-kind=StatefulSet --target-name=stash-demo --paths=/source/data --volume-mounts=source-data:/source/data --keep-last=5 --prune=true # For VolumeSnapshotter driver stash create backupconfig statefulset-volume-snapshot --namespace=demo --driver=VolumeSnapshotter --schedule=&amp;quot;*/4 * * * *&amp;quot; --target-apiversion=apps/v1 --target-kind=StatefulSet --target-name=stash-demo --replica=1 --volumesnpashotclass=default-snapshot-class --keep-last=5 --prune=true Options --driver string Driver indicates the mechanism used to backup (i.</description></item><item><title>Create Repository</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_create_repository/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_create_repository/</guid><description>kubectl-stash create repository Create a new repository
Synopsis Create a new Repository using Backend Credential
kubectl-stash create repository [flags] Examples # Create a new repository stash create repository --namespace=&amp;lt;namespace&amp;gt; &amp;lt;repository-name&amp;gt; [Flag] stash create repository gcs-repo --namespace=demo --secret=gcs-secret --bucket=appscode-qa --prefix=/source/data --provider=gcs Options --bucket string Name of the cloud bucket/container --endpoint string Endpoint for s3/s3 compatible backend -h, --help help for repository --max-connections int Specify maximum concurrent connections for GCS, Azure and B2 backend --prefix string Prefix denotes the directory inside the backend --provider string Backend provider (i.</description></item><item><title>Create Restoresession</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_create_restoresession/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_create_restoresession/</guid><description>kubectl-stash create restoresession Create a new RestoreSession
Synopsis Create a new RestoreSession to restore backed up data
kubectl-stash create restoresession [flags] Examples # Create a RestoreSession # stash create restore --namespace=demo &amp;lt;restore session name&amp;gt; [Flag] # For Restic driver stash create restoresession ss-restore --namespace=demo --repository=gcs-repo --target-apiversion=apps/v1 --target-kind=StatefulSet --target-name=stash-recovered --paths=/source/data --volume-mounts=source-data:/source/data # For VolumeSnapshotter driver stash create restoresession restore-pvc --namespace=demo --driver=VolumeSnapshotter --replica=3 --claim.name=restore-data-restore-demo-${POD_ORDINAL} --claim.access-modes=ReadWriteOnce --claim.storageclass=standard --claim.size=1Gi --claim.datasource=source-data-stash-demo-0-1567146010 Options --claim.</description></item><item><title>Delete</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_delete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_delete/</guid><description>kubectl-stash delete Delete stash resources
Synopsis Delete stash resources
Options -h, --help help for delete Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/tamal/.kube/http-cache&amp;quot;) --certificate-authority string Path to a cert file for the certificate authority --client-certificate string Path to a client certificate file for TLS --client-key string Path to a client key file for TLS --cluster string The name of the kubeconfig cluster to use --context string The name of the kubeconfig context to use --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --insecure-skip-tls-verify If true, the server&#39;s certificate will not be checked for validity.</description></item><item><title>Delete Snapshot</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_delete_snapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_delete_snapshot/</guid><description>kubectl-stash delete snapshot Delete a snapshot from repository backend
Synopsis Delete a snapshot from repository backend
kubectl-stash delete snapshot [flags] Options --docker-registry string Docker image registry (default &amp;quot;restic&amp;quot;) -h, --help help for snapshot --image-tag string Stash image tag (default &amp;quot;0.9.5&amp;quot;) Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups.</description></item><item><title>Download</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_download/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_download/</guid><description>kubectl-stash download Download snapshots
Synopsis Download contents of snapshots from Repository
kubectl-stash download [flags] Options --destination string Destination path where snapshot will be restored. --docker-registry string Docker image registry for restic cli (default &amp;quot;restic&amp;quot;) -h, --help help for download --host string Name of the source host machine (default &amp;quot;host-0&amp;quot;) --image-tag string Restic docker image tag (default &amp;quot;0.9.5&amp;quot;) --paths strings List of directories to be restored --snapshots strings List of snapshots to be restored Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups.</description></item><item><title>Kubectl-Stash</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash/</guid><description>kubectl-stash kubectl plugin for Stash by AppsCode
Synopsis kubectl plugin for Stash by AppsCode. For more information, visit here: https://appscode.com/products/stash
Options --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/tamal/.kube/http-cache&amp;quot;) --certificate-authority string Path to a cert file for the certificate authority --client-certificate string Path to a client certificate file for TLS --client-key string Path to a client key file for TLS --cluster string The name of the kubeconfig cluster to use --context string The name of the kubeconfig context to use --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) -h, --help help for kubectl-stash --insecure-skip-tls-verify If true, the server&#39;s certificate will not be checked for validity.</description></item><item><title>Trigger</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_trigger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_trigger/</guid><description>kubectl-stash trigger Trigger a backup
Synopsis Trigger a backup by creating BackupSession
kubectl-stash trigger [flags] Options -h, --help help for trigger Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/tamal/.</description></item><item><title>Unlock</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_unlock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_unlock/</guid><description>kubectl-stash unlock Unlock Restic Repository
Synopsis Unlock Restic Repository
kubectl-stash unlock [flags] Options -h, --help help for unlock Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/tamal/.kube/http-cache&amp;quot;) --certificate-authority string Path to a cert file for the certificate authority --client-certificate string Path to a client certificate file for TLS --client-key string Path to a client key file for TLS --cluster string The name of the kubeconfig cluster to use --context string The name of the kubeconfig context to use --enable-analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --insecure-skip-tls-verify If true, the server&#39;s certificate will not be checked for validity.</description></item><item><title>Version</title><link>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_version/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appscode.com/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.2/guides/latest/cli/reference/v0.2.0/kubectl-stash_version/</guid><description>kubectl-stash version Prints binary version number.
Synopsis Prints binary version number.
kubectl-stash version [flags] Options --check string Check version constraint -h, --help help for version --short Print just the version number. Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups.</description></item></channel></rss>