<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>v1alhpa1 API | Stash on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/v1alpha1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in v1alhpa1 API | Stash on Run production-grade databases easily on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/v1alpha1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Recovery Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/v1alpha1/recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/v1alpha1/recovery/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Recovery crd has been deprecated in v1beta1 api and will be removed in future version. Please use RestoreSession instead.
 Recoveries What is Recovery A Recovery is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition (CRD). It provides configuration for restoring a backup taken using Stash. You only need to specify the Repository, Snapshot and path you want to recover and volume where the backup will be restored.
Recovery Spec As with all other Kubernetes objects, a Recovery needs apiVersion, kind, and metadata fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restic Overview</title>
      <link>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/v1alpha1/restic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://appscode-v3-hugo.web.app/products/stash/v0.9.0-rc.0/concepts/crds/v1alpha1/restic/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Restic crd has been deprecated in v1beta1 api and will be removed in future version. Please use BackupConfiguration instead.
 Restics What is Restic A Restic is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition (CRD). It provides declarative configuration for restic in a Kubernetes native way. You only need to describe the desired backup operations in a Restic object, and the Stash operator will reconfigure the matching workloads to the desired state for you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>